Welcome to visit 17TRACK website, application,devices,and other related software under DEMON NETWORK TECH CO., LTD. (hereinafter referred to as "we" or "17TRACK")

This policy applies to all features and services of the 17TRACK products we provide, including mobile apps, websites, mini-programs, Tracking API, and the Shopify application. Before using any of the features or services we offer, please read and thoroughly understand this policy. Please start using them only after confirming your full understanding and agreement.

To safeguard your rights, this privacy policy will explain how 17TRACK-related products collect, use, and store your personal information, as well as the rights you have. Before using 17TRACK-related products and services, please read, understand, and agree to this policy.

Before using 17TRACK product services, please carefully read and thoroughly understand this privacy policy. Begin using them only after confirming your full understanding and agreement. We will periodically check and update our policies, so please visit this page regularly to ensure you are aware of the latest version of the privacy policy.

Any use or continued use of 17TRACK related products and services indicates your consent to the collection, use, storage and sharing of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

This policy will help you understand the followings:

1.How we collect your personal data.

2.How we use your personal data.

3.How we share, disclose and transfer your personal data.

4.How we store your personal data.

5.How we protect your personal data.

6.Your rights.

7.How we process the personal data of children.

8.How we transfer your personal data globally.

9.How We Use Cookies and similar technologies

10\. Changes to this policy

11.Contact us

Appendix One: List of Third-Party SDKs (Android App Only)

### **1.How we collect your personal data.**

In order to provide services to the Users ("User", "you", "your"), to optimize our services, and to protect account security, 17TRACK will collects information that you voluntarily provide, authorize, or generate as a result of your use of the Services when you register, use the Services, in the following manner:

* When you register for an account or log in to an existing account: 17TRACK will legally collect your e-mail address, cell phone number, login password, account nickname, and company name;
* When you use the Waybill Tracking feature, 17TRACK collect your waybill number and waybill tracking information;
* When you use the SHOPIFY APP plugin for product shipping and tracking 17TRACK will collect your email address, store name. 17TRACK collect your order buyer's email address, name, phone number, address, and order information;
* When you are invoiced for your purchase of 17TRACK products 17TRACK will collect your invoice information including invoice number, company address, and tax ID number;
* In order to provide internet services, 17TRACK will collect your internet information including IP address, cookies when you use 17TRACK services;
* On Android devices, when you agree to the Privacy Policy, 17TRACK may collect your Android ID, GAID, SIM card, SD card data, SN and other associated information.

The above information is a unique identifier assigned by Google to an Android device and is used to identify the device and not the individual. 17TRACK collect the above information for the purpose of optimizing the service experience, such as providing personalized services, improving application performance, and troubleshooting. Please note that the above information alone cannot identify a specific natural person.

In order to comply with the necessity of legal obligations, please note that it is not possible to identify a specific natural person solely on the basis of information such as the waybill number and the tracking information of the waybill. In order to optimize our products, 17TRACK may collect non-personal information about you. If 17TRACK combine such non-personal information with other non-personal or personal information to identify a specific natural person, the non-personal information will be treated as personal information.

2.Device Information:

When you use the 17TRACK app, in order to provide and improve our services, safeguard account security, and perform data analysis, 17TRACK may collect information about your device, including but not limited to Android ID, GAID, SIM card, SD card data, SN, device brand, device model, system platform, and operating system version. This information will help us identify the device, troubleshoot problems, provide personalized services, and prevent fraud.

3.Special note on Android ID:

17TRACK collect Android ID and other related information for the purpose of:

* Securing the service: With Android ID and other related information, 17TRACK can identify the device, prevent malicious attacks and fraud, and protect your personal information and account security.
* Optimize service experience: Combined with Android ID and other related information and other device information, 17TRACK can analyze your device usage, optimize service performance, and provide a more personalized experience.
* Data Analysis and Improvement: 17TRACK may use Android ID and other related information for anonymous data analysis to understand user behavior and improve our products and services.

The way 17TRACK collect Android ID and other related information is through the 17TRACK application automatically when you use the Services, without you having to provide it manually. The scope of collection is limited to the necessary device information and does not involve your private content.

Please understand that the functions and services 17TRACK provide to you are constantly updated and developing. If a certain function or service is not described above and collects your information, 17TRACK will separately explain the content, scope and purpose of the collection of information to you by means of page prompts, interactive processes, website announcements, etc. to obtain your permission.

| Index | Device Permissions | Business Functionalities | Description of Function Scenarios | Can it be Turned Off? |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| 1   | Storage Read/Write Permission | User saves tracking number | Used to save tracking number barcodes to the phone gallery in lower version Android devices. | Yes |
| 2   | Camera Access Permission | Scan Tracking Number | Used for users to open the camera and quickly add tracking numbers by scanning barcode for easy tracking. | Yes |
| 3   | Clipboard Read Permission | Conveniently query tracking number | Used for users to conveniently query after copying logistics tracking numbers and entering the app. | Yes |
| 4   | Device Brand | Recording of replacement equipment | Review of issues | Yes |
| 5   | Device Model | Recording of replacement equipment | Review of issues | Yes |
| 6   | System Platform | Record the source of feedback on issues | Review of issues | Yes |
| 7   | System Version | Recording of replacement equipment | Review of issues | Yes |

When you use the 17TRACK application, the app may request access to various permissions on your primary device. These permissions are summarized as follows:

### **2.How we use your personal data.**

The data collected during the provision of our services may be used in the following ways:

* Providing Services to You: We collect and store certain types of information about your use of the website to enhance its operation, enable service provision, and accurately assess the website's performance.
    
* Transaction Information: When you purchase our services, we collect information about the transaction, such as service details, purchase/refund dates.
    
* Communication with You: We use your personal information to communicate with you. You may receive notifications through email or mobile push notifications, such as updates on your package status or announcements about new services or promotions. You can unsubscribe at any time.
    
* Service Improvement: Assisting in designing new services and improving existing ones.
    
* Surveys and Marketing Activities: Involving you in surveys related to our products and services, conducting service-related market activities, and providing you with the latest information and promotional offers.
    
* Assisting Authorities: Assisting national judicial, administrative, and security authorities in conducting investigations and complying with applicable laws and regulations, as well as fulfilling other commitments to authorized agencies.

### **3.How we share, disclose and transfer your personal data.**

We will not sell, rent, trade, or otherwise disclose your personal information to anyone under any circumstances, except in the following special cases:

* Service Providers and Suppliers: For the management, supply, and improvement of 17TRACK services, as well as for marketing purposes, we may disclose personal information, including transaction information, to service providers and suppliers. Examples include logistics companies, suppliers, payment service providers such as PayPal, hosting and maintenance providers, data storage and management providers, marketing and promotional providers, and providers of email and SMS notifications. This is used to help us improve our services and products.
    
* For providing logistics insurance services: In order to offer you value-added services, including shipping insurance, we will share your personal information, order details, and logistics data with Seel Insurance Company when you choose the logistics insurance service. This is done to ensure that we can provide you with the requested logistics insurance service.
    
* Protection of Legal Rights and Other Legal Purposes: We may be required to disclose information, such as being subpoenaed, appearing in court, or being requested by law enforcement personnel for investigation, or for any other situation where the law requires us to disclose such information. We may also disclose personal information when necessary to protect our legal rights or to enforce our terms of use and other agreements. 17TRACK may provide your personal information in response to a search warrant, subpoena, or other valid legal query or command, or other requirements of applicable law.
    
* Mergers and/or Asset Sales: We generally do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to any third-party companies in the normal course of business. However, we may be acquired, merged, or acquired by another company, or we may dispose of some or all of our assets. In such cases, your personal information may be disclosed to another company, but this will be subject to the privacy policy in effect.
    
* Non-Personal Identifiable Information: We may share information that cannot identify you personally or any other individual with third parties (such as advertising partners), such as your tracking number and logistics tracking information, and the daily number of visitors to specific pages on the 17TRACK website.

### **4.How we store your personal data.**

Your personal information for your 17TRACK account will be transferred and stored on Tencent Cloud servers in Guangzhou, China, and also synchronized and stored on Tencent Cloud servers in the United States. Other personal information will be transferred and stored on Tencent Cloud servers in the United States. Unless the law requires or allows a longer retention period, we will retain the information collected from you or about you for the shortest time necessary to achieve the purposes described in this privacy policy. When the information is no longer needed for these purposes, we will either delete it or retain it in a form that does not identify you. In determining this retention period, we will consider various criteria, including the type of service requested or provided, the nature of our relationship with you, the impact on the services we provide to you if we delete certain information, and the legal requirements for retention. Please note that when you successfully apply to deactivate your 17TRACK account, we will promptly complete the review of your account deactivation. Upon approval, we will completely delete your personal data. If we cease to operate a product or service, we will notify you in a manner of individual delivery or announcement, and we will delete your personal data after discontinuing the product and service. \*\*

### **5.How we protect your personal data.**

We take industry-standard security measures to safeguard the personal data you provide from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, modification, damage, or loss. We will implement the following reasonable and feasible measures to protect your personal data:

* We use encryption technology to ensure the confidentiality of data.
    
* We employ trusted protective mechanisms to prevent malicious attacks on data.
    
* We have implemented access control mechanisms to ensure that only authorized personnel can access personal data. We conduct security and privacy training courses to enhance employee awareness of the importance of protecting personal data.
    
* We use secure encryption technology to protect your personal data during the transmission process. We take all appropriate organizational, managerial, and technical measures to ensure the security of the personal data you provide within our internal organization.

If our physical, technical, or managerial security measures are violated, resulting in unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction of data, thereby causing harm to your legal rights, we will take responsibility. In the unfortunate event of a personal data security incident, we will promptly inform you in accordance with legal requirements. This notification will include the basic details of the security incident, potential impacts, measures we have taken or will take to address the situation, advice on how you can independently prevent and reduce risks, and any remedial measures taken on your behalf. We will inform you of the relevant details of the incident in a timely manner through methods such as email, letters, phone calls, push notifications, etc.

While our business is designed to protect your personal information, please understand that there is currently no 100% security anywhere, whether online or offline. A 17TRACK account requires a username and password for login. Please safeguard your username and password, and do not disclose them to third parties.

### **6.Your rights**

In accordance with relevant local laws, regulations, standards, and prevailing practices in your countries and regions, we ensure that you have the following rights over your personal data. You have the right to request from us:

a)Access to Your Personal Information:

You have the right to access your personal information, except where exceptions are specified by laws and regulations. If you wish to exercise your right of data access, you can do so through the following methods:

Account Information: If you wish to access or edit your personal profile information in your account.

The path in the App: Home page → Click on the bottom-left corner "My Account" → Click on the top-left corner "My Account" to enter the personal information display page → Browse through nickname, country or region, email.

The path in the Web: Personal homepage → Click on the top-right corner profile picture → Expand the popup and click "My Account" → Browse through nickname, country or region, email.

b)Correct Your Personal Information:

When you discover errors in the personal information about you that we process, you have the right to request corrections. You can make correction requests through the methods listed in "1. Access to Your Personal Information."

If you are unable to correct your personal information through the provided link, you can contact us using the contact information specified in this Privacy Policy. We will respond to your correction request within 5-7 working days.

c)Delete Your Personal Information:

In the following circumstances, you can request the deletion of personal information by sending an email to us:

* If our processing of personal information violates laws and regulations.
    
* If we collect and use your personal information without obtaining your consent.
    
* If our processing of personal information violates our agreement with you.
    
* If you no longer use our products or services, or you have deactivated your account.
    
* If we no longer provide products or services to you.

If we decide to respond to your deletion request, we will also notify entities that have obtained your personal information from us to promptly delete it, unless otherwise provided by laws and regulations, or these entities have obtained your independent authorization.

d)Deactivate Your Account:

You may deactivate your previously registered account at any time. You can do so by following these steps:

For App Users: Homepage → My Account → Deactivate Account.

For Users of Other Services: You can send an email requesting account deactivation using the contact information provided in Chapter Eleven of this privacy policy. We will respond and process your request within 5-7 working days after verifying your identity. After deactivating your account, we will cease providing products or services to you and immediately delete your personal information.

e)Request a Copy of Your Personal Information:

You have the right to obtain a copy of your personal information. If you need to obtain a copy of the personal information we have collected about you, you can contact us using the contact information provided in Chapter Eleven of this privacy policy. We will respond and process your request within 5-7 working days after verifying your identity. We will provide a copy of your personal information via email. In compliance with relevant legal requirements and where technically feasible, we will provide you with a copy of your personal information as per your request.

f)California Resident Consumer Rights:

Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), California residents have the right to know, access, and delete their personal data. California residents also have the right to opt out of the sale of their personal data and to not be discriminated against for exercising their privacy rights. We do not sell your personal data to anyone for any purpose, nor do we discriminate when responding to privacy rights requests.

If you are a California resident, please be sure to review this privacy policy for important information about your rights under California privacy law and how to submit requests based on those rights

g)EU Data Protection Laws:

Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), as a data subject, you have the following rights regarding your personal data:

* Right to Know: You have the right to know how your personal data is being processed, including the purposes of processing, the types of data, the retention period, and the identities of recipients of the data.
    
* Right to Access: You have the right to access your personal data and may request a copy of the personal data we hold about you.
    
* Right to Erasure (Right to be Forgotten): In certain circumstances, you have the right to request the deletion of your personal data, especially if the data is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was processed, if you have withdrawn consent, or if the processing of the data is in violation of the law.
    
* Right to Opt Out of Data Sales: Under GDPR regulations, you have the right to ensure your data is processed lawfully, fairly, and transparently. You also have the right to choose not to have your personal data sold, which is a safeguard for your privacy.
    
* Right to Non-Discrimination: You should not face discrimination when exercising any of the above rights.

We do not sell your personal data for any purpose.

We will not discriminate against you for exercising your privacy rights, such as accessing, deleting data, or opting out of the sale of your data.

h)Response to Your Requests:

For the requests mentioned above, we will respond within 5-7 working days. Please refer to Chapter Eleven for our contact information.

In the following circumstances, we will be unable to respond to your requests:

* Requests related to the obligations of the personal information controller as required by laws and regulations.
    
* Requests directly related to national security and defense security.
    
* Requests directly related to public safety, public health, and major public interests.
    
* Requests directly related to criminal investigation, prosecution, trial, and enforcement of judgments.
    
* Requests where the personal information controller has sufficient evidence to show that the data subject has subjective malice or is abusing rights.
    
* Requests necessary for the protection of the life, property, and other significant legitimate rights and interests of the data subject or other individuals, but it is difficult to obtain the consent of the data subject.
    
* Requests where responding to the data subject's request would cause serious harm to the legitimate rights and interests of the data subject or other individuals or organizations.
    
* Requests involving trade secrets.

### **7.How we process the personal data of children**

a)We Encourage Parental Guidance for Minors

We expect parents or guardians to guide minors under the age of 14 in using our services. If you are a minor under the age of 14, you should read and agree to this policy together with your parents or other guardians before using our products.

b)We Value the Protection of Minor's Personal Information

We protect the personal information of minors in accordance with relevant laws and regulations. In cases where we collect personal information of minors with parental consent, we will only use, share, or disclose this information when permitted by law, with explicit parental or guardian consent, or when necessary to protect the minor.

c)Self-Inspection and Feedback Reception

If we discover that we have collected personal information of minors without obtaining verifiable parental consent, we will make efforts to promptly delete the relevant data. Additionally, we have established strict rules for the collection and use of personal information of minors to ensure the security of children and adolescents' personal information. If you are the guardian of a minor and have concerns about the personal information of the minor you are supervising, please contact us through the contact information provided in this policy. \*\*

### **8.How we transfer your personal data globally.**

We globally commit to handling and transferring personal information in compliance with the highest privacy protection standards. When you use our services, your personal information may be transferred to Tencent Cloud servers located in Guangzhou, China, and the United States. Such international transfers will follow strict data protection and privacy security measures to ensure a level of privacy protection equivalent to what we provide locally.

For personal information transferred to Tencent Cloud servers in Guangzhou and the United States, we adhere to relevant privacy and data protection laws in China and the United States, including but not limited to ensuring the existence of appropriate security measures such as encryption and access controls to safeguard data security and privacy. Additionally, we monitor changes in relevant laws to ensure that our practices can adapt promptly to these changes, safeguarding user privacy rights.

For personal information of EU users, we will conduct data transfers in accordance with the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This means that when personal information leaves the European Union and the Economic Area, we will transfer it by adopting standard contractual clauses recognized by the European Commission or when the receiving country has an adequate level of data protection. We commit to regularly assess the data protection level in the receiving country and ensure the effective implementation of protective measures.

If you have questions or need assistance regarding the cross-border transfer of your personal information, please contact us.

### **9.How We Use Cookies and similar technologies**

We use Cookies and similar technologies to enhance your experience with this service. When you use this service, we may use these technologies to send one or more Cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device, collecting and storing information about your visits and usage of the service. We commit not to use Cookies for any purposes other than those described in this privacy policy. We primarily use Cookies and similar technologies to achieve the following functions or services:

* Accelerate navigation
    
* Track website usage
    
* Identify user identity, access permissions, and preferences
    
* Conduct research and diagnostics to improve our content, products, and services

You can manage or reject cookies or data analytics tools through your browser settings. However, please note that disabling cookies or data analytics tools may impact your ability to enjoy the optimal service experience, and some services may not function properly.

**Strictly Necessary Cookies**

| Cookies | Cookies used | Expiration |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_yq\_bid | Protecting the security of web services. | 1 year |
| Country | Record the user's region or country to optimise the experience. | 1 week |

### **10\. Changes to this policy**

To ensure that you are always aware of how we collect, use and disclose your information, Dymax reserves the right to post any changes or updates to this Privacy Policy on this website and encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Policy for the most current information. Once we change this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating the "Last Updated Date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

### **11.Contact us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or require further information, please feel free to contact us at any time by one of the following methods

Contact person (Data Protection Officer): Hou Yi

Address: 3204 , Building 11 Tian An Cloud Park,NO.2018,Xuegang Road,Bantian

Phone number: +86-0755-86171718

Email:bis @17track.net

### **Appendix I: List of Third-Party SDK (Android Apps Only)**

To enhance our research and development efficiency and provide users with more diverse services, DEMON NETWORK TECH CO., LTD. uses third-party software development kits (SDK) in the 17TRACK Android app. These SDK are typically provided by third-party vendors to help improve app functionality and performance.

The SDKs we use include:

* QQ Login SDK (used to support QQ authorization login and account binding, which may collect user device identification information).
    
* WeChat Open Platform SDK (used to support WeChat authorization login and account binding, which may collect user device identification information).
    
* Alipay SDK (used to support Alipay authorization login and account binding, which may collect user device identification information).
    
* Facebook SDK (used to support Facebook authorization login and account binding, which may collect user device identification information).
    
* VK SDK (used to support VK authorization login and account binding, which may collect user device identification information).
    
* Firebase SDK (used to support push notifications, analysis, and statistics of application errors, which may collect user device identification information).
    
* AdMob SDK (used to display ads in the mobile app, sourced from the Google Ad Network, with location-based restrictions for specified regions, which may collect user device identification information).

### **Appendix II: Developer Information**

In the interest of transparency, we hereby add the full developer information:

Developer : DEMON NETWORK TECH CO., LTD

Phone number: +86-0755-86171718

E-mail: [bis@17track.net](mailto:bis@17track.net)
